<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Jake Hayes on Jake Hayes</title>
        <link>http://jakehayes.net/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Jake Hayes on Jake Hayes</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        
            <language>en-us</language>
        
        
        
            <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
        
        
            <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        
        <atom:link href="http://jakehayes.net/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
            <item>
                <title>Posts</title>
                <link>http://jakehayes.net/posts/</link>
                <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                
                <guid>http://jakehayes.net/posts/</guid>
                <description></description>
            </item>
        
            <item>
                <title></title>
                <link>http://jakehayes.net/about/</link>
                <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
                
                <guid>http://jakehayes.net/about/</guid>
                <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;jake-hayes&#34;&gt;Jake Hayes&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A software developer from Columbus, Ohio, who graduated from The Ohio State University, with a degree in Geographic Information Science and a minor in Design. Currently, I work as a software consultant supporting the client’s main customer management system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;programming&#34;&gt;Programming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My passion is learning new technologies and ways to implement them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;python&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am highly experienced with Python—a highly versatile language I have used in a variety of settings, including :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Geospatial analysis (arcpy)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Simple web scraping (beautiful soup, requests)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A simple Discord bot (discord.py)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic level web applications (django and flask tutorials)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excel scripting (openpyxl)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easy CLI applications (Click)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Testing (pytest)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;go&#34;&gt;Go&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My main focus with this language has been on backend web development with some CLI applications as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;javascript&#34;&gt;JavaScript&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the language of the Internet, JavaScript is a critical component to any web developers portfolio. I have taught myself a variety of JavaScript frameworks and have supported an internal project that used React. I have also used Vue.js in multiple personal projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;design&#34;&gt;Design&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With my background in design, I have an affinity for the aesthetics of software. I also enjoy making both mobile and desktop wallpapers and use whatever application will help me complete my vision the best. I am not afraid to venture into unknown applications and languages, as I strive to create the best possible outcome for my clients.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;adobe-illustrator&#34;&gt;Adobe Illustrator&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am well versed in Adobe Illustrator My work has focused on logo designs, book cover illustrations, holiday celebrations, and web pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;adobe-photoshop&#34;&gt;Adobe Photoshop&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photoshop is another avenue of expertise. Digital painting, photo editing, and photo compositions are just a few examples of the work I have done. In my free time I have edited I a variety of sports related graphics for fun, as this is a passion of mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;other&#34;&gt;Other&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adobe Creative Cloud products, including InDesign, XD, Premiere Pro, AfterEffects, and Lightroom, round out my repertoire of experience. As an eager and avid learner, I seek out opportunities to learn new programming languages and applications. No job is too small and no one will out work me or out learn me. I would welcome the opportunity to show you and your business all the possibilities I can create for an innovative, leading-edge web presence.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
